いらっしゃいませ
Welcome.
That'll be 420 yen.
420円になります
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
She probably seemed familiar because her hair looked...
ふとよぎったのは
きっと指の下ではねるこの姿は
a little like this, curling under my finger.
ほんの少し似ていたせい
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
matezu ni toozaketeitta no wa watashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta keredo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ      翻译 慧慧   日校 慧慧 低音子
总校 喵儿 AL   时间轴 葛蔓    压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
There's nothing to do.
暇だわー
There's always nothing to do.
暇なのはいつものことじゃない
This is different. Very different!
状況が違うの　状況が
ほら　最近文化祭やらなんやらで
Don't you remember how we shone doing this and that at the cultural festival?
輝いちゃったんじゃん　俺たち
いきなりまた平凡な生活に戻されてもつまんないわけよ
Suddenly going back to our ordinary lives is boring.
Yeah.
ねえ　見事に授業中もやることないもんね
And there's nothing to do during class, either.
Well, shouldn't you be paying attention to class during class?
いや　授業中は授業を受ければいいんじゃないですか
Anyhow, let's have lunch.
ま　とにもかくにも昼飯　昼飯
I'm so hungry.
腹が減っては
Seriously?
まじかよ
Huh? What?
Wet Paint
Do Not
Enter
Cafeteria-Store
よーへ　憧れの学食デビューだぃ
Making my big debut in the famous school cafeteria!
It's been a while since we last came here.
久しぶりだね　学食来るの
あっ　あそこ空いてますよ
There are some free seats over there.
ま　せっかく学食に来たんだし
Well, we did come all the way down here, after all.
Udon
Soba
Yam
udon/soba
Seaweed
Tanuki
udon/soba
Tempura
Kitsune
udon/soba
Ramen
Miso Ramen
Shio Ramen
Pork Ramen
Saury
noodles
Curry
Curry Pork
Katsudon
Oyakodon
Chinese
Rice Bowl
Stamina
Bowl
Daily
Special A
Special B
Vegetable
udon/soba
So cheap!
安　うどん250円って
Udon for 250 yen!
思ってたより結構メニューあるね
They have more on the menu than I expected.
All right!
よーし　ここのメニュー全部制覇してやるぜ
I'm gonna conquer everything on their menu!
That might be difficult.
いや　制覇は厳しいよ
日替わり定食が立ちはだかるから
They have daily specials.
毎日メニュー違うもんね
It's different every day.
What? Then I'll have to come here every day!
えっ　そんなの毎日来ないといけないじゃん
That's right. This day will never come again.
Tempura udon/soba
Ramen
そうだよ　今日という日は二度と来ないよ
軽々しく制覇なんて口にできねぇな　学食
Complete domination of the menu is easier said than done!
Get out of the way.
どけ
What are you doing, Kanamecchi?
何にすんだよ　要っち
It's your fault for just standing there.
ちんたらしてんのが悪いんだよ
As if I'll let you get in front of me!
させるか
一番に注文するのはこの千鶴様
The first one to order shall be me, Chizu—
ふえーっくしょん
Achoo.
H-Hey! Come on, Yukki! What was that for?
ちょ　ちょっと　ちょっと何すんの　ゆっきー
Sorry. Just caught a little cold.
ごめんごめん
今ちょっと風邪引いてて
Cough, cough.
次の人
Next.
Um, kitsune udon, large size.
ええと　きつねうどん大盛り
超健康じゃん
You're not sick at all!
チックショウ　卑怯な
Miso Ramen
Damn it.
That cheater.
Shun-chan!
春ちゃん　こっちこっち
Over here.
What is it?
どうしたんですか
食堂でシンデレラが働いてんだよ
Cinderella's working in the cafeteria!
あー　本当だ　きれいな人ですね
You're right. She's beautiful.
I know, right?
ゆっきー！　ゆっきーも見て　ほら
Yukki!
Yukki, look! Over here!
Yeah, yeah, I saw.
はー　うん　見た見た
What's wrong with you? You're no fun.
んだよ　もう食い付き悪いな
まあ　あんなもんだから　祐希君の周囲への関心なんて
Well, that's how it is mostly. Yuuki-kun's not all that interested in his surroundings.
Excuse me...
あのう
はいよ
Yes?
I thought I ordered kitsune udon...
俺きつねうどん頼んだと思ったんですけど
What?
えっ　あら　いやだ　おばちゃんてっきり
Oh my, it completely slipped my mind. I'm sorry!
ごめんね
嫌いじゃなかったらこのてんぷらも食べちゃって
You're welcome to have the tempura, too, if you'd like.
えっ　でも
But...
Oh, it's fine, take it. Just think of it as a token of my love for you.
いいのいいの
おばちゃんからの愛だと思って　軽く受け取って
あたしも後20歳若けりゃねえ
If only I were twenty years younger...
余計軽く受け取れない
You're making it harder to take it.
Everyone, there's a cougar-killer over here!
（注：マダムキラーとは? 〔和madam＋killer〕既婚の女性たちを夢中にさせるような、魅力的な男）
皆さん　マダムキラーがここにいますよ
あったかいご飯にきれいなシンデレラ
With its warm food and a beautiful Cinderella,
the cafeteria's a pretty great place.
いいもんだね　学食ってのは
屋上そろそろ寒いし
It's getting cold up on the roof.
暫くこっちで食べる
Why don't we eat inside for a while?
いいですね
Good idea.
I agree!
賛成
What?
Someone's not happy with your idea.
ここにええとか言ってるやつがいんぞ
I won't be able to collect the stickers if we eat here every day.
だって毎日学食になったらシール集まんないじゃん
Stickers?
シール？
Yeah, from the convenience store.
うん　コンビニのやつ
パンについてるシールを30点集めるとお皿がもらえんの
If I collect thirty points from buying bread, I get a plate.
んだよ　まだ9点じゃねえか
You only have nine points.
That's what I mean...
だから毎日学食になったらシール集まんないじゃん
I'll never get enough if we eat here every day.
Why don't you bring your convenience store bread here?
じゃ　祐希はコンビニのパン持ってくれば
That won't work. Watching all of you eat cafeteria food...
そんなの　皆が学食食べてるの見たら
would make me want some, too.
絶対そっち食べたくなるじゃん
たまに面倒だな　この子は
He can be quite a handful sometimes...
はいはいはい　俺協力するっす
I got it, I got it! I'll help you!
皆もゆっきーのシール集めに協力しようぜ
Let's all help Yukki collect stickers!
You shouldn't say such things if you don't really intend to do them.
やめろよ　勢いだけでそういうこと言うの
I want to shine, as if I were reliving the festival!
もう　輝きたいの
文化祭アゲイン
Sure, but how?
いいけど　どうやって
コンビニのパン食べる人を日替わりで変えて
Why don't we rotate who eats the bread each day...
and give all the stickers to Yukki?
シールはゆっきーにあげるっつうのは
名づけてシール当番制
We'll call it "Sticker Duty!"
How ground-breaking.
なんか画期的
僕も協力します
I'll help.
いよし決定
It's decided! Let's start tomorrow.
じゃ　さっそく明日から始めようぜ
Who'll go first?
誰からやりますか
はいはいはい　俺がやる
Me, me, me! I'll do it!
なんでおまけしてくれないの
Why won't you give me any extra?
うちはおまけ受け付けてないので
We don't hand out freebies.
That's a lie.
うそだね
だって俺見たもん
I saw you give someone tempura and fried tofu.
天ぷらと油揚げ両方もらってるやつ
もしかしてあれかな
Is he talking about the mix up with Yuuki's udon?
祐希のうどんが波紋投じちゃってるかな
シンデレラピンチィ
Cinderella's in trouble!
Go help her out.
おい　お前助けに行ってこいよ
Why?
なんで
Don't say that. Hurry up!
なんでじゃねえ
早く行け
Cinderella's a delicate girl who can't stand up for herself!
シンデレラっていうのはいじめられても
何も言えないか弱き女の子なんだよ
And she's still waiting for her prince to ride up on his white horse!
そして白馬の王子の登場を今か今かと待っているんだよ
ってお前が行くのかよ
Wait, you're going?!
ねね　お願いってば
Come on. We're growing boys.
俺たち育ち盛りなんだよ
じゃーさ　おまけしてくれたら今度映画に
If you give us something extra, we'll take you to the movies—
しつこい
Enough.
What?
おまけの一つ二つで騒いでる僕ちゃんたちと映画
You think I'd want to go to a movie with little boys who make a fuss over extra food?
女誘うなら　自分で稼げるようになってからにするのね
You should learn to support yourselves...
before you even think about asking out a girl.
いや　昼間のシンデレラはすごかったな
Cinderella was amazing at lunch.
She really shut them up.
一瞬にして黙らせちゃうんだもんな
千鶴出番なくて
You just grabbed a towel and came back,
since there was nothing for you to do, Chizuru.
布巾借りて戻ってきたもんね
Tsk.
Shut up!
煩いわ
俺が王子になるのはやっぱ本命の子の前だけってことだよ
It just means I'll only be a prince for my one true love!
Your one true love?
本命？
Never mind, never mind.
Cafeteria-Store
Excuse me!
すいません
Yes, thanks for waiting.
はいはい　お待たせ
あら　お昼はごちそうさまでした
Oh!
Thanks for lunch.
You run the store?
購買もやってんの
Yes. Sorry, but we're about to eat lunch.
そうなのよ　ごめんね
おばちゃんたちこの時間がちょうど昼ご飯で
ええと　それで何を
Did you need something?
Yukki, she's asking you what you want.
ゆっきー　何買うのかって
Oh, that.
あれ
Can I have that, please?
あれください
That?
あれって
That, please.
あれください
Silly boy!
いやだよ
My daughter is-not-for-sale!
うちの娘は売り物じゃあーりーまーせーん
Wh-What were you th-thinking?!
おま　お前いきなり何言ってんだ
There's an order to these things!
順序ってもんがあるだろう
You start with something like an exchange diary!
まずは交換日記とか
That's not what I meant.
そうじゃなくて
Kayo, Kayo! Come here!
花代花代　ちょっと来て
何　お母さん
What is it, Mother?
この子があんたに用があるんだって
This kid's got business with you!
What?
何
Um, I was wondering if I could have that...
えと　それをいただけないかなーと
食べかけだけど
It's half-eaten.
I mean the bag.
じゃなくて　袋の方
袋　別にいいけど
The bag? Sure.
Actually, I wanted the sticker.
いえ　そのシールがほしくて
The sticker? I can't give you that.
シール　これは無理よ
Just give him the sticker, Kayo!
あー　もう
シールぐらいあげたらいいんじゃないか　花代
だってあたしこのシール集めてるんだもん
I'm collecting them. He can't have it.
ダメよ
Can't you make an exception?
そこを何とか
ほら　こんなに必死にお願いしてるんじゃないか
Come on!
He's really desperate!
How do you figure that?
どこが
あんた　自分で集めなさいよ
Collect them yourself instead of taking them from others.
人からもらわないで
でも
But I need to collect thirty points' worth, and it's difficult.
俺30点も集めないといけないっていう過酷な状況で
So does everyone else!
皆そうだから
いいだろう　お皿くらい
Who cares about one little plate?
You already have some, you know!
あんたにはあれがあるじゃないか
I gave you the Yamawaki bread plates.
お母さんがもらった山脇パンのお皿
Don't say that in front of them!
You're embarrassing me!
やめてよ　人前で恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいのはこっちだよ
I'm the one who's embarrassed!
女手一つで育てた娘が
The daughter I've raised as a single mother won't even give someone a measly sticker!
シールの一枚も快く譲れないなんて
That has nothing to do with stickers!
それとシールは関係ないでしょう
Why are you so stubborn?
どうして
Do you know how hard I've worked to collect these stickers?
これだけ集めるのにどれほど苦労したか
I'm so embarrassed that my face is on fire.
I'll never give it away.
絶対あげないんだからね
You And I
Oh, sorry.
すみません
You really are collecting stickers.
シール本当に集めてるのね
あっ　購買の
You're the girl from the store.
You came to buy bread, didn't you?
パン買いに来たんでしょう
Extremely delicious.
Juicy Sausage
シール当番が始まるから毎日買わなくてもよくなったんですけど
I don't need to buy bread every day,
because we're starting Sticker Duty,
でも　自分でも買った方が点数早くたまるし
but I'll get points faster if I buy bread as well,
so I'm not sure what to do.
どうしようかなと
何そのシール当番って
What's Sticker Duty?
あんた眠いの
Are you sleepy?
いえ　普通ですけど
No, I'm fine.
I see.
あっそう
でも珍しいわね
It's unusual for a high school boy to want a plate.
男子高生がお皿ほしいって
こういうの好きなの
You're into this sort of thing?
Bread Festival
Anpanda
The Brave Plate
I guess.
まあ
Hm...
I'm collecting stickers because I like them, too.
ま　私もこういうの好きだからシール集めてんだけどね
Do you read anime magazines?
アニメ雑誌とか見ます
Huh? What magazines?
あ？　何雑誌
Guess not.
違うのか　何だ
What magazines?
何雑誌
いえ
Nothing.
Hey, how many points do you have?
ね　あんた今どのぐらい点数たまってんの
何にウケました
What's so funny?
ごめんごめん
Sorry. It's just cute that you've got only got one point stickers on your sheet.
可愛いぐらいに1点が並んでるなって
So many two's and three's... and a four.
2点3点がいっぱい
あっ　4点も
4点のパンなんて学生には買えないもんね
A student can't afford a bread worth four points.
ま　これが給料もらってる社会人
Just goes to show what a working adult with a salary can do.
大人ってやつよね
っていうか　4点って
Did the four point sticker come from the extra large yakisoba bread?
めが盛り焼きそばパンですか
Wh-Why does that matter?
I've just wanted to try it for a while.
わ　悪い
前からちょっと気になってたのよ
食べ切ったんですか
Did you finish it all?
Why do you care?
それが何か
Are you sure?
大丈夫
I've gotta go.
It's fine. No one will know.
大丈夫　ばれない　ばれない
俺もう行くんで
I guess I don't have to get one today.
やっぱり今日はいっか
Huh?
あれ　このパンシールがない
Red Bean Bread
This one doesn't have a sticker.
Wait!
ちょっと待って
あんたたち　このパンについてたシール　取ってたでしょう
You girls...
You took the sticker off this bread, didn't you?
What?
Don't give me "what". The sticker.
えじゃなくて　シール
買ってないのにシールだけ剥がすとか
You can't take the stickers without buying the bread!
そういうずるしないの
ほら　シール
Hand it over.
あー　最近の若い子はもう
Kids these days...
あれ　あの子は
Huh? Where'd he go?
ちょっと　何逃げてんのよ
Why'd you run away?
だって店でシールシール叫ぶ人ってあんまりいないし
No one screams about stickers in a store.
I'm pretending I don't know you.
他人のふりしますよね
Wh-What's with that?
な　何それ　私だって好きで叫んでるわけじゃ
I didn't yell because I wanted to!
じゃ　あんたは平気なの
Are you saying you don't care...
パン買ってもない人がシールどんどん集めちゃっても
if people take stickers without buying the bread?
それはいやですけど
I do care.
See?
ほら
What a ridiculous morning.
もうなんなの　朝っぱらから
What?
何
Nothing.
いいえ
You should get to school.
あんたも早く学校行きなさい
遅刻するわよ
You'll be late.
Right...
Huh? Yukki.
ゆっきー
早いね　千鶴にしては
You're up early.
今日俺シール当番だから
I'm on Sticker Duty today,
so I thought I'd buy it before school.
学校行く前に買ってこうって思ってさ
Then, I recommend the extra large yakisoba bread.
だったらめが盛り焼きそばパンがお薦めだよ
何それ
What's that?
Can't you enjoy your food more?
お前さ　もっとうまそうに食えねえのかよ
こっちまで飯まずくなんだろう
You're making mine taste worse.
But it's so hard!
だってきついだもん　これ
Chizuru, don't you usually put away two slices of bread easily?
千鶴いつもはパン二つぐらい楽勝でしょう
It's mentally challenging!
じゃなくて
精神的にきついの
皆は学食なのに
You're all eating cafeteria food,
and I have to eat convenience store bread.
俺一人コンビニパンでさ
I feel left out.
なんか仲間外れっぽい
What are you saying?
何言ってんの
シール当番考えたの千鶴でしょう
You're the one who came up with Sticker Duty.
It's your own fault.
自分のせいだよ
No, it's your fault to begin with.
いや　元を正せばお前のせい
It's fine! Just wave your delicious food in my face while you're eating it.
いいよいいよ
じゃそうやって皆して俺に見せびらかしながら食べればいいじゃん
Ah, this bread's so good!
あーー　パンおいしいな
千鶴君　これどうぞ
Ah, Chizuru-kun, take this.
ありがとう　春ちゃんだけだよ　いつも俺にやさしいのは
Thanks! You're the only one who's always nice to me, Shun-chan.
Don't baby him, Shun.
甘やかすな　春
He'll never learn if you keep that up.
お前がそんなんだから
いつまで経ってもこいつのあほが治んねえんだよ
What did you say?
何を
俺にいっつも意地悪ばっか言う要っちにはこうじゃ
Since you're always mean to me, take this!
何食ってんだよ　てめは
What do you think you're eating?
You won't miss one.
Besides, it's not even that good.
いいじゃん　ちょっとぐらい
そんなにおいしくないよ　このから揚げ
Then spit it out! Come on!
じゃ　今すぐ吐き出せよ　おらおら
Stop it! You'll make me drool out the juice!
やめてよ　ジューシーな肉汁が流れるじゃないか
めちゃめちゃうまそうじゃねえか
Sounds like it's delicious!
Not true!
Quiet down.
ちょっと静かにしてよ
You bonehead! Spit it out!
いいじゃないの
Spit it out!
What's wrong with them enjoying their meal?
ご飯はやっぱり賑やかに食べてもらわないと
もう　そうやって甘いこと言って
You're too nice to them.
いいじゃない
Isn't it nice to see them getting along?
仲良子よしで
どう見たって
They're that loud because they're obviously not getting along.
仲悪いから騒がしいことになってんじゃない
Shun-chan!
春ちゃん
茉咲ちゃん
Masaki-chan.
I'm surprised you knew we'd be here.
ここにいるってよく分かりましたね
I figured you'd be here since they blocked off the roof.
屋上入れないようになってたから
ここかなって
S-Sorry. Looks like you're not done eating.
ご　ごめんね
まだ食べ終わってなかったね
That's okay.
大丈夫ですよ
お勉強ですか
Do you need help with your homework?
What are you having trouble with?
どこが分からないんですか
This one.
あー　ここは僕も苦労しました
I had trouble with this one, too.
You did?
え　春ちゃんも
Yes. You should start by solving this bit here.
はい
まずは先にこっちを解いていくといいですよ
Oh, I see.
そうなんだ
What's wrong with you?! Don't get in the way!
もうなんなのよ　さっきから
邪魔しないで
I don't even care.
いいもんいいもん
I'll just eat the food Shun-chan gave me.
春ちゃんにもらったおかず食べちゃうもん
Huh? It won't come out.
あれ　出ない
What's wrong with this thing?
なんだよ　これ　ちくしょ
Damn it. There!
Boys' Bathroom
Sorry, Shun-chan.
ごめんな　春ちゃん
It's okay.
大丈夫ですよ
授業始まっちゃいますね
Class is starting.
If it doesn't get washed off now, it'll stain!
いや　でも今洗わないと浸みになっちゃうし
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Well, I'm the one who got it on you.
いやいや　俺がぶちまけたんだから
Hey...
あーのさ
Yes?
はい
Shun-chan, do you not have one?
春ちゃんはーいないの
Not have what?
何がですか
Well... as in...
だから...その…
someone you like?
好きな人とか
I mean...
いいや　なんとなくね
I just thought it'd be nice to talk about stuff we don't usually discuss!
普段しない話も新鮮でいいかなみたいな
あくまで
Someone I like?
好きな人ですか
Not at the moment, I guess.
まだいないかな
I see.
そっか　そっか
Chizuru-kun, what about you?
千鶴君はいないんですか
What? M-Me?
えっ　お…俺
F-For me, w-well...
俺はもうそれ　それはもう
春ちゃんでーい
it's Shun-chan!
倒れちゃう　千鶴君
I'm falling, Chizuru-kun!
I hope your uniform doesn't stain.
浸み残んねえかな　制服
大丈夫ですよ
It's fine.
I wonder about everyone else, though.
それより
皆はどうなんですかね
何が
Wonder about what?
好きな人いるんですかね
If there's anyone they like.
Wet Paint
Do Not
Enter
Oh, it's you!
あ！あんた　すっごいいいところに
Good timing! Could you wipe some tables down for me?
ちょっとテーブル拭いてくれない
俺ノート買いに来たんですけど
I came to buy a notebook.
あたし指切っちゃって
I cut my finger.
ほら
See?
I can't leave until I finish this, so I want your help.
これ終わらないと帰れないから
手伝ってほしいのよ
I'll come back tomorrow.
また明日買いに来ます
Hey.
Want some stickers?
あんた　シールほしくない
何点もらえます
How many points will you give me?
だからそうやって拭いちゃダメなんだって
Don't wipe them like that!
Don't push the crumbs from the table onto the floor!
テーブルの上の生ごみは床に落とさないの
We'll have to sweep the floor again!
また下掃かないといけなくなるでしょう
これ絶対3点じゃなきゃ割に合わない
This better be worth at least three points.
また　もう何度目よ
There you go again! How many times is that?
Hey, what are you going to do with the plate?
ね　お皿もらったらどうするの
カレーライスとかあれで食べるの
Are you going to eat curry rice on it?
カレーは食べないかな
I don't think I'd eat curry on it.
Huh?
The plate would probably turn yellow.
お皿が黄色くなっちゃいそうだし
まあ　多分カレーじゃなくても使わないまま終わりそうですけど
I probably won't use it for anything else, either.
What? You were listening?
話聞いてた
聞いてますよ　一応
I'm listening.
そうなのよね
You're right.
Even if you get the plate, you can't use it.
お皿もらっても結局使えないのよ
絵が可愛いから
The art's too cute!
でもうちのお母さんそういうの全然分かってくれないの
But my mom doesn't get it all,
so she always tries to use it.
すぐ使おうとするの
へえー
I see.
It's getting dark.
日が暮れちゃう
Pick up the pace. I need to go soon.
もうちょっとペースあげてよ
私早く帰らないと
どこか行くんですか
Are you going somewhere?
ううん　うち晩ご飯早いのよ
No, we just eat dinner early.
お母さん寝るのも早いから
My mom goes to bed early.
寄り道しないでちゃんと家でご飯食べるんですね
You go straight home to eat dinner?
うち片親だし
It's just my mom and me at home.
あたし一人子だし
一人で食べても寂しいでしょう　お母さん
I don't want to make my mom eat alone.
とか言って
She just watches TV when I'm not there, though.
あの人　私がいなくても
普通にテレビ見たりしてるけどね
終わった
Are you finished? Good work.
ご苦労様
Thanks for the help.
ありがとう
助かったわ
What about my sticker?
あの　シールは
Oh, I forgot.
忘れてた
Again...
また
Udon
Soba
Yam
udon/soba
Seaweed
Tanuki
udon/soba
Tempura
Kitsune
udon/soba
Ramen
Miso Ramen
Shio Ramen
Pork Ramen
Saury
noodles
Curry
Curry Pork
Katsudon
Oyakodon
Chinese
Rice Bowl
Stamina
Bowl
Daily
Special A
Special B
Vegetable
udon/soba
It won't come off. Sorry.
あー　ダメ　剥がれない　残念
もうちょっと粘ってくださいよ
Try a little harder.
ふーん　それで1点もらえたんだ
So you got one point.
That's great.
よかったね
That was definitely three points' worth of work.
絶対3点だったけどね　あの労働は
もらったシールってこれ？
Is this the sticker she gave you?
あ　そう　それ
Yeah, that's it.
でもさあ
She must be a really nice girl to give you a sticker when she's collecting them, too.
自分も集めてるのにくれるんだから
いい人だね
She's pretty, too.
きれいだし
きれい
Pretty...
No, she's not pretty.
いや　きれいではないよね
Really?
そう
Yeah.
Plate Giveaway
Plate Givea way
Point
It looked a little like this, curling under my finger.
それは指の下ではねるこの姿と少し似ていて
次にあの後ろ髪を見たのは
The next time I saw that hair was behind my eyelids.
瞼の奥
今日学食何食べよっかな
What should I eat at the cafeteria today?
祐希　今日シール当番じゃなかった
Yuuki, aren't you on Sticker Duty today?
What? No way.
えっ　うそ
Crescent Moon Silhouette
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
Giving me the chance to answer the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta dakedo
I hated how weak I was
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto wo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
Next time: Middle School Diary
Middle School Diary